https://kappamapgroup.com/privacy-policy/

Login / Signup
You have to be signed in to add & view your wishlist.
Login / Register
Shopping Cart
You currently have no items in your cart.
View full list in cart.
Total:
View Cart
Checkout
SHOP ALL
MenuBy DestinationNorth AmericaUnited StatesAlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaPuerto RicoRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUS Virgin IslandsUtahVermontVirginaWashingtonWest VirginiaWyomingWisconsinCanadaMexicoCentral AmericaSouth AmericaEuropeAsia CloseBy UsageTRAVEL MAPSAtlasesFolding MapsNational Parks & RecreationPopOut MapsWALL MAPSCity and County Wall MapsState Wall MapsUnited States Wall MapsWorld & Foreign Wall MapsClassroom Wall MapsHome & Office DecorMaps on Demand Customized MapsCenterPoint Customized Wall MapsMap AccessoriesEDUCATIONClassroom Wall MapsDeskpad MapsEducational AtlasesFlash CardsFolded Map PostersHistory Wall MapsNotebook MapsOutline Testing MapsReferenceRolled MapsState Thematic MapsCUSTOM MAPSPromotional MapsMaps on Demand®CenterPoint Maps™ROAD TRIP FUNAdult ColoringBooks & ColoringGeography Playing CardsLicense Plate GameKids’ Travel Activity BooksPuzzlesHOME & OFFICE DECORHistorical MapsAntique MapsUS Physical or PoliticalWorld Physical or PoliticalPrimary CloseBy Product TypeATLASESNorth America Road AtlasesState Road AtlasesCity & County Road AtlasesFOLDING MAPSCity & County Street MapsState & Regional Road MapsUS Interstate MapsWorld & Foreign MapsCoastal MapsWALL MAPSHome & Office DecorUnited States Wall MapsWorld & Foreign Wall MapsCity and County Wall MapsState Wall MapsClassroom Wall MapsMap AccessoriesMaps on Demand Customized MapsCenterPoint Customized Wall MapsROAD TRIP FUNKids’ Travel Activity BooksLicense Plate GameGeography Playing CardsPuzzlesBooks & ColoringAdult Coloring CloseBy BrandADCAmerican MapDeLormeHagstromKappa BooksKappa Map/Universal MapMaps.comMAPSCONational GeographicOther Close
Where do you want to go?
Pick a Region
Asia
Central America
Europe
North America
Canada
Mexico
United States
Kappa Map Group, LLC and Affiliates Privacy Policy
We take your privacy seriously, and we want you to know how we collect, use, share, and protect your information. “Kappa” means any entity that carries the Kappa brands, and any of our subsidiaries or divisions.
Your use of any of our sites is subject to the Conditions of Use for that site.
This Policy applies to:
The websites owned or operated by Kappa Map Group, LLC and any of our subsidiaries or related companies, unless that site has its own privacy policy; if it does, that policy applies.
Information we collect in mailings or phone calls to us and at other locations and events under the Kappa name.
For simplicity, we will call the Kappa websites “digital properties” throughout this policy.
What we collect
Information you give us
We collect and store information you provide through our digital properties and through mailings or phone orders.
The information we collect from you includes things like:
Name
Mailing address
Email address
Phone number
Credit card number and other payment information
In certain situations, we may also collect things like:
Demographic and lifestyle information (if you sign up for a birthday list)
Your responses to surveys
Information from other sources
We may receive information about you from other sources, including third parties that help us update, expand, and analyze our records and identify new customers, and provide products and services that may be of interest to you.
Information collected automatically online
We collect information about your interactions with us, including the type of device or browser you’re using, your IP address, your browsing behavior while on our website, and the URLs of the websites you were at before you visited our site (these are called “referring URLs”).
Kappa and our partners use technologies such as cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level.
We may permit third party service providers to collect and process some information from our digital properties. We may share personal information with those providers and may have similar arrangements with interest-based advertisers. We provide more information about interest-based ads below.
Our digital properties are not designed to respond to “do not track” requests from browsers.
Location information
Some of our digital properties may collect your location to help process orders.
In order for any mobile application to identify your location, you must enable location services through your mobile device’s settings. If you do not want Kappa to collect this information or to enable these features, you can turn off location services on your mobile device. Kappa has no control over your device’s settings.
Reviews and other content you provide
Our websites offer publicly accessible blogs or community forums. Be aware that anyone who accesses these areas may read, collect, and use the information you provide.
How We Use the Information We Collect
We use the information we collect for things like:
Identifying you on our websites in order to customize your experience (for example, based on your purchase history or your location)
Fulfilling orders and requests for products, services, or information
Processing refunds, returns, and exchanges
Tracking and confirming online orders
Marketing and advertising products and services
Conducting research and analysis
Information Retention
We may retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
How We Share The Information You Provide
We may combine or share information among current or future Kappa companies, including affiliates and subsidiaries.
We may share your information (including information about others that you have provided to us) with third parties to perform services on our behalf such as:
Fulfilling orders and delivering packages
Sending Kappa marketing communications
Fulfilling subscription services
Conducting research and analysis
To provide our customers with products or services we believe may be of interest to you or others, occasionally we may share our customers’ or gift recipients’ names and mailing addresses with other companies, agents, or brokers. At any time, you have the option to remove your name and address from lists we share with 3rd parties, by emailing us at info@kappamapgroup.com or by calling us at 386-873-3010.
Sometimes we may be required to share personal information for legal reasons, for example, if we are required to do so by a regulation, court order, subpoena or other legal process. We may also share information when we believe it’s necessary to comply with the law or to respond to a government request, or when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect Kappa, our customers, or others.
We may share personal information in the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, dissolution, or similar event. If such an event takes place, we’ll notify you through e-mail (if we have your email address) and/or a prominent notice on our applicable website(s) of any change in ownership, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.
How We Protect Your Information
We use a variety of information security measures to protect your online transactions with us.
We use reasonable security measures to protect the confidentiality of personal information under our control and appropriately limit access to it.
We are committed to protecting your information, but you can do your part. You should create a strong password and protect against unauthorized access to your password and your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer and do not share your password with anyone. We cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and by using our digital properties you acknowledge that you do so at your own risk.
Your Choices
You may at any time:
Stop receiving marketing or promotional e-mails, direct mail, phone, and mobile marketing communications
Update and correct your personal information
Deactivate your account
Request removal of information you post on our digital properties. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your content or personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.
To do any of these, let us know by one of these methods:
Follow the directions in a marketing e-mail, direct mail, or mobile communication that you receive from us
Provide your request and current contact information through one of the contact methods listed under “Contact Us” below.
Please note: Even if we are able to anonymize or make your content or information no longer visible, this does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of your content or personal information from the Internet.
Protecting Children’s Privacy
We are committed to protecting children’s privacy on the Internet and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.
Links to Other Websites
Our websites link to other websites, many of which have their own privacy policies. Be sure to review the privacy policy on the website you’re visiting.
Social Media Features
Our website includes ways to interact and share using social media, through features such as the Facebook “Like” button, the “Share This” button, or interactive mini-programs that run on our website (“widgets”). These features may collect information such as your IP address or the page you are visiting on our website, and may set cookies to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features can be hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the social media company providing the feature.
Privacy Policy Updates
We may need to update our Privacy Policy as we and our customers grow and evolve. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or practices please contact us.
Phone:
386-873-3010
E-mail:
info@kappamapgroup.com
Address:
Kappa Map Group, LLC
112 E. New York Ave
DeLand, FL 32724
Company Kappa Map Group provides the largest selection of map titles of any US map publisher.
Mailing List Signup Sign up to get interesting news and updates delivered to your inbox.
Leave this field empty if you’re human:
© 2019 Kappa Map Group, LLC. All Rights Reserved.
Privacy Policy
Conditions of Use
FAQs
